Total Experience: 1 Year(s) 8 Month(s)

Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Highest Degree: NA [na]

# Pournima Patle (1) Featured

Associate Software Developer seeking roles in Software Development, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, JavaScript, Angular6, Nodejs, Elasticsearch, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Express, loopbe



Current Designation: Associate Software Developer - Mean

Stack

Current Company: Valuefy Solution Pvt Ltd

Current Location: Mumbai

Pref. Location: Mumbai, Nagpur, Pune

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Associate Software Developer, Software Development, Application Maintenance, Project

Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution

Architecture, JavaScript, Angular6, Nodejs, Express, Loopback, Elasticsearch, CSS3, Bootstrap, JavaScript, Jquery, Ajax, MongoDB,

MySQL

Verified: Email - id Phone Number I

Last Active: 20-Jan-21 Last Modified: 20-Jan-21

## Summary

Overall 1.4+ year of experience in the development of Web & Enterprise applications (Wealthfy And CRM) using MEAN stack Technology. Hands on experience in Angularis, Nodejs, Mongodb, Express, Mysql Knowledge, Elasticsearch, Loopback, Strongloop, Visual studio code tool, Kibana for the development of Mean stack project. Hands on experience in Angular 5, Angular 6, Javascript, Git, NPM. Cohesive team worker, having strong analytical, problem solving and interpersonal skills

## Work Experience

Valuefy Solution Pvt Ltd as Associate Software Developer - Mean Stack Jun 2019 to Till Date

Backend Developer (Node js)

BridgeLabz Pvt Ltd. as Fellowship Engineer Feb 2019 to Jun 2019

#### **Education**

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from SGBAU in 2018

PG: NA (na) in 0

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

Diploma in Computer Technology Engineering

#### IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
Javascript, Angular6			
Nodejs, Elasticsearch			
HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap			
Javascript, Jquery, Ajax			
ORACLE, MS-SQL			
EXPRESS			
Visual studio code, kibana, Jira			
Mongodb			

## Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Marathi				

## **Projects**

Project Title: BARCLAYS/EQUIRUS

Client: Barclays/Equirus

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Jan 2020 - Till Date Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Skill Used: Angular 5, Nodejs, Mongodb, MySql, ElasticSerach, RabbitMQ, Jquery, Visual studio, Kibana, Jira

Project Details: Dealing with clients and solve client query and support them to updation of functionality as per requirements adding new functionality. Upload instruments and product and manage the data. Transaction of client aggregation, report generation, export PDF Maintain the data and replicate it into the elastic search.

Project Title: HDFC Offshore

Client: HDFC Bank

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Sep 2019 - Dec 2019 Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Skill Used: Nodejs, Mongodb, Oracle, Mysql, Elasticsearch, RabbitMMQ Loopback, Git Project Details: Wealthy product manage the wealth and investment of Client Wealthfy

is for the bank there Operation team they can manage their client and investment of client and aggregated investment of day to day life and generate report of client and etc. Included in product.

Backend API development, Bloomberg integration, PDF development, PPT development in their pie chart and all restful api as per client requirement to provide solution for wealth management customer and investment of the project.

Project Title: Fundoo Notes Application

Client: BridgeLabz Solutions Nature of Employment: Full Time

Duration: Mar 2019 - Jun 2019 Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Skill Used: Nodejs, Mongodb, Express, Angular 6, Redis, HTMPL, CSS, Loopback

Project Details: Material Responsive Design, Card Based UI, Navigation

Panel, Search & Show notes in list & grid view etc. Each card was designed with an about editor, toolbars & menus.

Understanding on AWS Services i.e. EC2, S3 & also deployed the application using CI/CD with Jenkins

#### **Affirmative Action**

#### Work Authorization

1/22/2021 https://freesearch.naukri.com/preview/printResume?uname=d541e762026e042870ecf3536e660c6e5d0b0c551e1a0e455643100b0f...

Physically Challenged: No Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time